I was excited thinking about how excited
she would be to get this plant
the next day
I find myself wearing a shirt that says
cow itch don't kill my vibe
that plant was a hassle
to bring in that vanilla bean plant
yeah I didn't even have space
but I made the space
because she was a client who became a friend
most people I meet on Facebook Marketplace
we become friends
cause we speak about plants and common interests
a few times
she talk about the idea - how much more flavorful
chocolate bar and
vanilla ice cream would be if
she could like grow her own chocolate and
vanilla bean and process them
I'm helping to bring this vision to life
when I go with the plant to surprise her
she don't want it
she was telling me to keep it and grow it
I don't just take a plant and and grow it like that
I always prepare prepare the environment
prepare a feeding plan for it
I saw the opportunity I had her in mind
and to how she talk about this idea
and this vision of having her own vanilla bean
I thought she would at least be semi prepared
for something like that
for a vanilla bean
at first I thought that
she was probably thinking about what the price was
gonna be
I made it clear that this is a gift from a friend
to a friend it's a gift don't cost right
because she always spends with me yes
she always buy plants
and basically she was nervous about growing it
she didn't have the confidence that she could grow it
she wasn't confident that she had the right
environment and everything
but she does well with house plants and flowers
that's what she grows well
she don't consider herself a flowers person
she don't really care for flowers and house plants
really
but seeing her yard you would think otherwise
other people try to grow the plants that she grows
people who love those type of plants
they don't do well with it
that situation leads me to ask people
what type of plants do you grow
not the type of plants that you want to grow
not the type of plants that you love growing
but the type of plants that you actually grow currently
because it's what you're doing currently
that we can really give you the most assistance with